One of the things that's been helpful with AI
is finding documentation or
explanations of code for Bow
Torch, which is very underdeveloped and doesn't
have a lot of documentation for it.
And so it does a really good job of finding explanations
for what functions do or how to organize,
like how to call functions and use data because
it's hard to find good examples of how
I can use them in my own code.
For us, I think,
for the powder doser, it's been, um, clot has
been controlling the whole thing, writing the
code that does the tests and running the tests.
And it's been really nice in a lot of ways, particularly
that it can also record the data.
So it runs the test and it records all the data
in a really good way. And it's the primary one
looking back at the data, so it knows where everything
is.
And they can automatically draw conclusions on
the data, and like the data analysis part of
it as we're, um,
like,
concurrently running tests, it's been really
nice. The scary part of that is that I,
even if I think I could probably figure out somewhat
quickly how to run the powder dust to myself
and write the code,
I have not done that, and I don't currently know.
Like, if you asked me to do it myself, I couldn't
do it right now. It would take me a couple of
days, probably.
Um,
yeah, that's scary.
We were talking about the idea that the human
element is important in research, especially
when you're putting your name on it.
that if I'm doing research,
like,
if Claude is doing research, then anybody can
push the button,
and then Claude is doing research.
If I'm doing research, it should have aspects
of me in it, it should have that human element,
that it's specific to me, and
my ideas, and my work.